// Name: Tran (Teryl) La
// Seneca Student ID: 150353175
// Seneca email: ntla1@myseneca.ca
// Date of completion: Jan 23th, 2019
// WORKSHOP 2
// I confirm that the content of this file is created by me,
//   with the exception of the parts provided to me by my professor.

WORKSHOP 2 

The reason for the significant time difference between the copy and move operations:
You are not require to allocate memory in Move so you save more time. Moreover, the move semantic is only moving the 
object instead of copying it. This might invove copying pointers to some resources and then setting them to nullptr,
 so they cannot be used to access the resources anymore. 
The goals of the semantics are different: 
Copy: make a copy of one object to another
Move: move ownership of the resources from one object to another (much less expensive)
I had to review getline(), get() and open(), close().

In this workshop, the part I struggled most with was the 1 argument constructor. This is mainly because the instructor is quite
vague, so I had to navigate a lot with my other classmates, hence the late submissions. Otherwise, the other parts are rather easy.
I find that OOP345 instructions are way less clear than OOP244 and it creates a lot of confusion and most students submmitted their work late.
In_lab was way more difficult than at_home. I wish we got more resources and help with the labs.
The Move semantics are really straight-forward.

QUIZ 2 reflection:

I only got the move assignment constructor wrong.

I wrote: 
Class-name operator=(Class-name&&);
Instead of :
Class-name& operator=(Class-name&&);